Office of Physical Planning Records, 1869-1994 (bulk 1946-1994): Finding Aid AC154
University Archives
- Series 1: Building Project Records, 1879-2002 July 2; 91 boxes
  - Women's Crew Facilities Plaque, 1981; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 35)
  - Chapel Railings, 1979-1982; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 36)
  - Dillon Gym - Ramps, 1980; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 37)
  - Campus - Main Entrance, 1980; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 38)
  - Inscriptions - Chapel - Frederic E. Fox, Murray-Dodge - Class of '81, 1981; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 39)
  - Class of '45 Memorial Map Room, 1981; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 40)
  - Fire Escape Maintenance - Blair Arch Steps - Railing, Henry-Foulke - Railing, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 41)
  - Fluid Dynamics - Sketch, 1981; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 42)
  - Aaron Burr Hall - Display Window, 1982; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 43)
  - Stair Rails - 1903 Hall, Stevenson, 1915 Hall, 1982; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 44)
  - Corwin, Woodrow Wilson - Handicapped Access, 1982; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 45)
  - Bio-Chemical Sciences Building - Plaques, 1979; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 46)
  - Moffett Hall - Plaques, 1982; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 47)
  - Macmillan Building - Entrance Vestibule, 1983; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 48)
  - Plaques - Firestone - D'Agostino, Frederic E. Fox '39, 1983; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 49)
  - New South - Entrance Railings, 1983; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 50)
  - Parking Lots - Playing Field Steps, 1984; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 51)
  - Lot 12 - Railing, 1984; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 52)
  - Nassau Hall - Partitions, 1984; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 53)
  - Wainwright Plaque Sketch, 1983; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 54)
  - William S. Dix Plaque, 1984; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 55)
  - Notestein Hall - Plaque, 1984; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 56)
  - Inscription - Sarah Edwards, 1985; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 57)
  - Chapel Inscription - Waite, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 58)
  - Peyton Hall - Railing, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 59)
  - Wilcox Hall - Railing, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 60)
  - Green Hall - Railing, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 61)
  - Firestone - Industrial Relations Section Plaque, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 62)
  - Chapel - Leh Memorial, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 63)
  - Woodrow Wilson Plaque - New Jersey Seal, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 64)
  - Observatory Guest House - Railing, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 65)
  - Dillon Generator Stack, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 66)
  - Nassau Hall - Handicapped Entrance, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 67)
  - Plaque - Keyes-Emerson, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 68)
  - "Campaign for Princeton" Plaques, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 69)
  - Lourie-Love Field - Sign, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 70)
  - '52 Field Scoreboard Sign, 1987; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 71)
  - Class of '46 Garden Inscription, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 72)
  - Chapel - Swain Inscription, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 73)
  - Cappon-Green "Bench" and Plaques, 1984; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 74)
  - Ronald A. Rogerson Plaque, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 75)
  - Weaver Endowment Plaque and Benches, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 76)
  - Martin Herbert Eisenhart Plaque, circa 1985; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 77)
  - Fine Library - Wilks Memorial, 1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Vivian Plaque, 1985; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - McCosh Health Center - Plaques, 1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Jadwin Physics - Ballantine Room - Rail, 1984; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Griffin Memorial Bench - Plaque, 1981-1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Bowen-Rudenstine Clapper, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Princetoniana Committee, 1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - H. White Prize Plaque, 113 Dickinson Hall, 001 Fisher Hall, 1982, 1990; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Firestone Library Plaques, 1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1879 Lions, 1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1987 Ivy Stone, 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Gulick Field Scoreboard, 1990; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - "Gabo" Sculpture Wind Bracing, 1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Chapel Gate Hardware, 1989; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Putnam Sculpture Relocation, 1988; 1993; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Putnam Collection - Original Labels, 1973-1994; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Fitzrandolph Gate Model, 1990; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Maclean House - Trophy Case, 1990; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Maclean House - TV Cabinet, 1990; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Chapel Inscriptions, 1988-1991; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Chapel Inscriptions, 1989-1992; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Chapel Inscriptions, 1992-1994; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - 1857 Bell: Plaque Studies, 1992; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - 1857 Bell: Preliminary Studies, 1992; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Einstein Fireplace and Syrian Arch for Math Department, 1978; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - Frederick Fox of Math Department, 1977; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Eno Hall Alterations, 1970; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - New South: Balanced Doors Study, 1972; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - McCormick Gates: Jadwin, 1972; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 29)
  - 101 Foulke, 1973; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 30)
  - McCosh Room 011, 1973; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 31)
  - E-Quad Library Doors, 1969; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 32)
  - Edwards Place: Porches, 1973; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 33)
  - Acoustic Problems, 1971; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 34)
  - Fairman Plaque, 1973; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 35)
  - Inscriptions, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 36)
  - Dorm - Second Egress, 1973; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 37)
  - Woodrow Wilson Bust Pedestal, 1973; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 38)
  - 185 Nassau Street, 1974; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 39)
  - Arthur Strang Plaque, 1969; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 40)
  - Nassau Hall - South East Asia Inscription, 1974; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 41)
  - Forrestal Exits, 1975; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 42)
  - Robert Winters Tiger Pedestal, 1983; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 43)
  - McCosh 10 - Handicapped Lift, 1983; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 44)
  - William S. Dix Plaque, 1975; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 45)
  - Various Photographs: Buildings, Rooms, Plaques, Etc, 1962-1983; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 46)
  - Books, Publications, and Reports, 1914-1991; 1 box
    - "Feasibility Study for the Improvement of the Architecture Building, Princeton University," Appendices A-D, 1991; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - "Feasibility Study for the Improvement of the Architecture Building, Princeton University", 1991 January 15; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Tree Survey, Princeton University - McCarter Theater, Faculty Row and Graduate School, 1986 October 27; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Tree Survey, Princeton University - Main Campus, 1985 March 22; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Vice President for Facilities - Correspondence - Report, 1977; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Dober, Campus Planning, 1963 June; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Larson and Palmer, Architectural Planning of the American College, 1933; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Dean Mathey, Men and Gothic Towers, 1967; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Condit, "Princeton Engineering School", 1962; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Princeton Dormitory Study, 1977 September; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - List of Trees on the Princeton Campus, 1964 October; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - "The Trees at Princeton University", 1964 December 21; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Condit, "Princeton Engineering School", 1962; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - "The Trees at Princeton University", 1964 December; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Stadium, 1914; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Physical Plant for Selected Academic and Administrative Departments, 1961 November; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Drawings for various projects, 2002 July 2; 3 boxes
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    AR.2009.059
    - East Pyne, 2002 July 2; 1 box (Box 97)
    - Little Stadium, undated; 1 box (Box 98)
    - Dod, Patton, Joseph Henry Boathouse, undated; 1 box (Box 99)
  - Plans for the Restoration of Nassau Hall, 1900; 1 box (Box 100)
    AR.2005.062
  - Plans for 81 Alexander Street (Forbes College) and the Dunwalke Estate, 1927-1929; 1 box (Box 100)
    AR.2005.063
  - Chapel Inscriptions, 1929-1963; 1 box (Box 101)
  - Henry House alterations, 1961; 1 box (Box 101)
- Series 2: Architectural Drawings (Microforms), 1870-1985; 11 boxes
  Series 2: Architectural Drawings (Microforms) consists of microform aperture cards containing blueprints, floor plans, and other architectural drawings of campus buildings. For the most part, each group of cards represents one building or landscape feature, a related group of buildings, or drawings of a similar type, e.g., "Planting, Parking and Plazas" or "Sanitary Sewerage System." The parenthetical notes next to each title are a shorthand system of identifi employed by the Office of Physical Planning. Though the number of images varies from building to building, there exists a basic floor plan and elevation for each structure. Notably absent from this set of plans is any depiction of Nassau Hall.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of structure or subject.
  - Alexander Hall (ALEX), 1900; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Alexander Street Buildings (AXS), 1926; 1 box
    - 80 Alexander Street, 1926; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - 112-115 Alexander Street, 1926; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - 126 Alexander Street, 1926; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - 136 Alexander Street, 1926; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Annual Events (ANN), 1934; 1 box
    - Cannon Green, 1934; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Clarke Field, 1934; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Dillon Gymnasium, 1934; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Fine Library, 1934; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - The Front Campus, 1934; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Jadwin Gymnasium, 1934; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Pardee Field, 1934; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - University Gymnasium, 1934; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Woodrow Wilson School Plaza, 1934; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Aqueduct Road Buildings (EGT), 1974; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Architectural Building – School of Architecture Building (ARCH), 1962; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Architectural Laboratory (AL), 1929; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Armory (ART), 1925; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Biochemical Sciences Building (BIO), 1976; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Blair Hall (BH), 1896; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Blairstown Summer Camp (BC), undated; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Boathouse (BO), 1954; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - Boiler House (BOI), 1954; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - Union Boiler No. 1 (BOI A), 1960; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - Union Boilers Nos. 2 and 3 (BOI B), 1962; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 25)
  - Broadmead (BR), 1923; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 26)
  - 171 Broadmead (PCD), 1929; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 27)
  - Brown Hall (BRN), 1937; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - Building No. 25 (NR), 1946; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 29)
  - Building No. 29 (STL), 1946; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 30)
  - Butler Tract Housing (BU), 1946; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 31)
  - Caldwell Field House (CFH), 1961; 1 folder (Box 87, Folder 32)
  - Campbell House (CA), circa 1908; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Cannon Club (CAN), 1973; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Cap and Gown Club (CG), 1907; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Chapel (CP), late, 1920s; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - 6 Charleton Street (CHA), 1985; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - College Road, Apartment 8 (COA), 1977; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - 87 College Road (CO), 1956; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - College Road Faculty Apartments (CRF), 1960s; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Computer Center (CC), 1970; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Corwin Hall (WW), 1950; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Cuyler Hall (CUY), 1912; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Cyclotron (CYC), 1966; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Dial Lodge (DL), 1916; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Dickinson Hall (DIC), 1929; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Dickinson Street Buildings (DS), 1929; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Dillon Gymnasium (GM), 1945; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - University Gymnasium and Old Outdoor Gym (GS), 1927; 1 folder (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Dod Hall (DOD), 1930s; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Dodge Hall (DG), 1930s; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Dodge-Osborn Hall (DO), 1959; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Dunwalke (DUN), 1920s; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - East Pyne Hall (PAB), 1950s; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Edwards Hall (ED), 1880; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Edwards Place (EDP), 1970s; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Elm Club (EC), 1920s; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Energy Research Laboratory (ERL), 1970s; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Engineering Quadrangle (EQ), 1960s; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Engineering Quadrangle Library Alterations, 1974; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Eno Hall (EN), 1923; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Road (FR), 1960; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Farrand Memorial (FM), 1960; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Feinberg Hall (FB), 1985; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Ferris-Thompson Faculty Houses (FHO), 1947; 1 folder (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Fine Hall (MATH), 1966; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Firestone Library (LIB), 1954; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Firestone Library Addition 1971 (LIB AD), 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Firestone Library, Dulles Wing (LIB DW), 1961; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Firestone Library, Reserve Room (LIB RBR), 1973; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Firestone Library, Periodicals Room (LIB PR), 1976; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Firestone Plaza (FP), 1976; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - 120 and 139 Fitzrandolph Road (DHE), 1922; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Forbes College (PI), 1961; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Forbes College (Princeton Inn) Addition (PIA), 1971; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Foulke and Henry Halls (FH), 1920; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Frick Chemical Laboratory (CL), 1925; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Frick Chemical Laboratory Addition (CLA), 1962; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Frick Chemical Laboratory Modernization Phase 1 (CLA), 1970s; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Frick Chemical Laboratory Modernization Phase 2 (CLT), 1970s; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Frick Chemical Laboratory Additions (CLU), 1984; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Gauss Hall (GA), 1959; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Geology Library (GUL), 1979; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Graduate College (GC), 1913; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Graduate College Dormitories (GCD), 1962; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Graduate College Extension (GCE), 1925; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Green Hall (GH), 1926; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Green Hall Addition (HEL), 1950; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Guyot Hall (GU), 1906; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Guyot Hall Additions (GUA), 1960; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Hamilton Hall (HA), 1910; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Joseph Henry House (HE), 1930s; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Holder Hall (HOL), 1909; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Hoyt Laboratory (BIO), 1977; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Jadwin Gymnasium (JG), 1965; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Jadwin and McCormick Memorial Gateways (JDM), 1972; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Jadwin Physics Building (JPB), 1965; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Joline Hall (JOL), 1932; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Jones Hall (FI), 1932; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Lake Carnegie (LA), 1923; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Lenz Tennis Center (LTC), 1983; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Little Hall (LITH), 1898; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Lockhart Hall (LOC), 1928; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Maclean House (DH-2), 1940s; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Macmillan Building (GB), 1960; 1 folder (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Madison Hall (DIN), 1915; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - McCarter Theater (MT), 1924; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - McCormick Hall (MCH), 1942; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - McCosh Hall (MC), 1907; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - McCosh Infirmary (INF), 1924; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous A-R (MI), 1934-1982; 1 box
    - Athletic Association Fields, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Alexander Street, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Concrete Borings, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Catch Basin Covers, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Campus Maps, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Canoe House, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Clubs on Prospect Avenue, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Central Mail Improvement, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Dormitory Rentals, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Drainage Plan, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Drains, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Development of University Field Area, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Jonathan Edwards Inscription on Slab in Princeton Cemetery, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Electrical Standards Symbols, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Elm Drive Realignment and Guard Booth Removal, 1982; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - Fence, Guard Rail on Washington Road, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - Farrand Memorial Bench, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 22)
    - Fire Alarm and Smoke Detection, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 23)
    - Fire Hydrants, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - Gates, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 25)
    - Glacial Boulder Inscription, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 26)
    - Guard Booth, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 27)
    - Gabo Structure, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 28)
    - Gas Lines, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 29)
    - South Gate (Proposed), undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 30)
    - Dodge gate, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 31)
    - Geology Field Camp, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 32)
    - Gas Cylinder Storage Building, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 33)
    - Harrison Street Bridge, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 34)
    - John Hibben Memorial Tablet Inscription, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 35)
    - Hibben Garden, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 36)
    - Hospital Fete, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 37)
    - HVAC, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 38)
    - Key and Seal Club, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 39)
    - Kiosk, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 40)
    - Lots 5 and 6, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 41)
    - Monuments, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 42)
    - Moore Street and Jefferson Road – Development Area, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 43)
    - Manhole Covers, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 44)
    - Maps – Campus, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 45)
    - Maps – Borough, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 46)
    - Maps – Underground Services on Nassau Street, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 47)
    - Maps – Princeton and Environs, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 48)
    - Maps – Forrestal Campus, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 49)
    - Maps – Rowland Tract, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 50)
    - Maps – Tract at Princeton Junction, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 51)
    - Maps – Princeton Township, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 52)
    - Maps – Front Campus Design by Aymer Embury II, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 53)
    - Maps – Sites Adjoining Graduate College, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 54)
    - Maps – Water Company Property, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 55)
    - Maps – Mercer County, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 56)
    - Maps – Mercer County Map of Princeton, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 57)
    - Manhole Frames and Covers, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 58)
    - McCoy Memorial, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 59)
    - Map – Aerial, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 60)
    - Map – Geodetic, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 61)
    - Map – Campus, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 62)
    - Map – Contour of Borough, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 63)
    - 221 Nassau Street, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 64)
    - Oil Pollution Prevention, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 65)
    - Presbyterian Church, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 66)
    - Railroad Yards, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 67)
    - Railroad Property, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 68)
    - Railroad, Relocation of Station, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 69)
    - Railroad – Property Acquired in, 1934; undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 70)
    - Railroad – Property at Lake Carnegie, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 71)
    - Railroad Tracks, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 72)
    - Railroad Freight Station, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 73)
    - Railroad Property, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 74)
    - Roads, Widening College Road East of Stadium, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 75)
    - Roads, Nassau Street to Gym, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 76)
    - Roads, Gym to Witherspoon, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 77)
    - Rain Water Drains, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 78)
    - Road Closings, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 79)
    - Road to Lawrence Court, 1966; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 80)
    - Road Gate, Hydraulic, undated; 1 folder (Box 93, Folder 81)
  - Miscellaneous S-Z (MI), 1959-1984; 1 box
    - Storm Drainage, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Sun Dial, Mather, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Skeet Field House, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Storm Drainage, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Possible Suicide of Carolyn Drucker, 1978; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Stockton Street, #65, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Storm Drainage, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Telephone Conduits, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Trees, University Place, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Tennis Conduits, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Trees, University Place, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Tennis Courts, 1959; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Telephone Conduits, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Traffic Control Booths, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Tennis Courts, 1964; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Thompson Wall and Gateway, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Traffic Signs, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Telephone Conduits, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Thompson Memorial Court, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Trash Containers, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - Traffic Lights, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 21)
    - Traffic Improvement, 1984; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - Underground Utilities, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - Walks, McCosh to Chapel, Proposed, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 24)
    - Walks, West of Brown Hall, Proposed, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 25)
    - Walks, Paths and Islands, South Campus, 1965; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 26)
    - Walks, Improvements, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - Walks, Lawrence Court to Parking Lot, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 28)
    - Walks, Lot 20 to Fine Hall, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 29)
    - Wall, Proposed Stone Wall on University Place, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 30)
    - Washington Road, Pedestrian Crossing, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 31)